Now everyone has a very bad
ya todo el mundo tiene una muy mala
image of delux, nowadays the vast
imagen de delux a día de hoy la gran
majority of people, stanix and I warned him, we
mayoría de gente stanix y yo lo avisamos
said, man, you have to maintain your
le dijimos tío has de mantener tu
objectivity, you have to stop hanging around with
objetividad has de dejar de moverte con
Dallas and no, no, no, no, let's
Dallas y que no que no que no que
condemn kcu, let's condemn cku
condenemos a kcu que condenemos a cku
Dallas has gone to the podcast once and then
Dallas ha ido al podca una vez y luego
a debate, you have the balls to tell
un debate tiene huevos tú para decirle a
anyone who to hang out with And who not to
nadie con quién juntarse Y con quién no
when you're defending cocu and you
cuando estás defendiendo al cocu y te
go to the evening, suck up to ccu,
vas a la velada hacerle la pelota al ccu
man, if Javi Oliveira is a cancer,
tío d si el Javi oliveira son cánceres
I don't know how he came to the conclusion
yo no sé cómo ha llegado a la conclusión
that hanging around with those people is going to
de que moverse con esa gente le va a
add anything to him, that your most watched live show of
sumar algo que tu directo más visto de
your life is you in a corner While
tu vida es tú en una esquina Mientras
Dallas was fighting with someone else and you were
que el Dallas se peleaba con otro y tú
n't contributing absolutely anything because you're not
no aportando absolutamente nada porque
even worth being a moderator, four
es que ni para moderador vales cuatro
times he coincided at my house, all
veces que coincidió en mi casa las
four times I told him, enough with Dallas,
cuatro veces le dije basta de Dallas
enough with giving your opinion and taking
basta de dar tu opinión y de
sides, no man,
posicionarte a favor de no tío pues
then you're bad with Dallas, I
entonces estás malito con el Dallas o
mean, four times a person comes to your
sea cuatro veces va una persona a tu
house and you instead of talking about  Whatever you
casa y tú en vez de hablar de lo que tú
have to offer, you talk about Dallas,
tengas para ofrecer hablas del Dallas
enough with the condemnation, coscu, but come on, this
basta de condena coscu pero vamos esto
is already a joke, eh, but man, what has
ya es de traca eh pero tío Qué te ha
Dallas done to you? Has it shown you the
hecho el Dallas te ha enseñado el
blunderbuss to make you so traumatized?
trabuco para que te quedes tan traumado